My name is Egbuche Boyd Ikemefuna from Anambra state, Nigeria.
The person standing beside
me is my very good friend.
My testimony goes like this.
Starting from 2013, I felt sick
I thought it was Malaria, I started treating malaria.
I was treating malaria and I saw
myself going down critically.
Until the company I was working
for asked me to go home,
and check what the problem was with my health.
I said, "Okay!" and went home
I came back and told them its malaria
that am treating it.
They said, "Okay!"
To an extend that I started going down
that I couldn't move - nothing.
And they said, " Man go home!
and take care of yourself"
I went home, I went to he hospital and
I was diagnosed of chronic Hepatitis B
alongside inflamed appendicitis
I didn't discover it on time,
It was up to a year before I discover it.
It had gone far beyond every fiber of my being.
It had eaten up my livers
I was dying.
I thought its something money can do,
I thought money could buy my life back.
I started visiting hospitals
So many hospitals tried, they kept referring
me from one hospital to another.
To an extend that hospitals started rejecting me.
When I went to hospitals, they
didn't even admit me any longer.
They look at me, they look at my report and say,
"young man we cant help you
please go to another hospital."
We started tolling round hospital to hospital
my dad, my brother, everybody running around.
To an extend that I become critically down
If you saw me, you could ran away
I became like a skeleton I couldn't talk, eat or move
I was just lying down there.
Everybody started running away from me
because It was during the time of the outbreak of Ebola.
So everybody started running away from me,
to an extend that my immediate elder brother
said that he doesn't want to die.
That he is leaving home and that he is leaving town.
that he doesn't want to get infected
He ran away too.
It went on and on, I kept on pressing
from hospital to hospital.
Until I went with my dad to one
hospital and the doctor said,
"young man I want to tell you something,
where is your dad?"
I said, "this is my dad."
He said, "Father, take your son back
home, no doctor can help this guy,
medically, there is no way for him, he is
just standing next to his grave.
We cant do anything for him.
We cannot even operate on him
due to the chronic hepatitis B he is having and
the appendices in him is already inflamed."
He said that If they operate on me
they fear that I was not going to make
I gave them my consent that they
should do it,
that if anything happened there was no problem.
The doctor said that he doesn't
think anybody could do that,
that no doctor wants to have
anybody's blood on his hand.
That I should go home, if I know the God that
I am serving I should run to him
and pray to him.
Hepatitis B according to the doctors, they said that
it is an ailment that is worst than HIV.
The doctor said, that Its better
I have HIV than I have Hepatitis B.
And it was not just Hepatitis B,
it is a chronic Hepatitis B.
During the time I was going around in hospital
When I got to some hospitals
so many doctors were seeing me and scream
and run away.
Some of them were saying, "This guy!
I don't think this guy can make it.
And I was refereed to a specialist
at Enugu teaching Hospital
I got there and I met this lady
and I said, "Excuse me madam,"
She turned around and saw me, she scream, "Jesus!"
and run away.
I felt so bad, I had to go back home
and I decided never to go back to hospital again.
If you saw me then, I don't think
you would want to even stand close to me.
I was like a corpse, I was like a skeleton.
If you saw me even in clothes,
my bones were still showing it.
I was that bad.
So it went on and on, all hopes were lost, my family was crying.
My mum was asking, "God were are you?"
That you will not be alive and
anything will come and take away one of my best.
It got to an extend that I lost hope that
I was not going to make it anymore
I said to my self, "this is my end."
I would wake up every morning
and go behind the door of the backyard
and look at the space there and
wondered where will they bury me If I die.
Is it here or there?
At times my brothers will be eating, playing, laughing
and I will be looking at them and I would say to my self,
"one day I wont be seeing my brothers again."
I felt pain in me, It was the worst experience in life
for a man to be alive and know that he is dying
and there is nothing the doctors could do about it.
It was very very awful, I don't know how to say this.
But to God be the glory!
I was rejected, everybody ran away.
She was the only friend that stayed - of everybody.
She stayed, I told her....
The doctors told me that I should be very careful,
I should avoid physical contact with my family.
That I am highly contagious,
that they may contact it.
I started avoiding my family, I would
lock myself up in my room
instructed no one to come in,
but she refused, she stayed
She would forced her way in,
She would come, she clean me up.
I would tell her, are you not afraid?
You may contact this thing, and you may end up like me.
Go! don't come again, forget about me.
you've tried your best.
She said, No! that she believe
that nothing will happen to me.
That she believes, that even
if anything will happen to me,
that thing should come through her first.
It went on and on until luckily
my pastor introduce me to Emmanuel TV.
I started watching Emmanuel TV,
I saw what God is using our prophet.
'Our daddy' in the Lord, senior prophet TB Joshua
to do hearings, deliverance and all that.
I sermon courage to come
but I couldn't walk, I couldn't embark on a journey.
I couldn't sit in a vehicle for that long.
I didn't have money to board the flight
I wasn't that strong, no way to come.
I stayed, I said to myself, all hope is lost.
forget about it
It started coming to my mind that
I was tired of this life.
The symptoms, the often symptoms,
as if there were ants.
rolling inside my body.
And another symptoms of always shaking
as if I was having hypertensive disease.
I was shaking that I cannot
hold anything in my hand.
I cannot stand, I would fall down
All those symptoms were there
and it was very awful.
I was like let me just forget everything
In fact i was tired, I started
thinking of taking my own life.
To an extend, I said that I cant live anymore
If I have to commit suicide and go and rest,
then, so be it, so I started thinking,
trying and practicing it.
The way I could just end up my life
and go and rest.
But the more I would do it, a voice would tell me,
"So long as there is life, there is hope.
Dont give up!"
That voice kept on coming on and on.
But I kept on seeing myself going
down to an extend
that I started seeing and hearing
things that were not there.
I would be lying in my room and
I would be seeing people
and they would be taking to me.
But physically those people are not there.
And I would be talking back at them,
but when somebody comes in
would be like, "who are you talking to?"
I would say, "Ah, somebody."
I wouldn't see anybody again.
It happened and it went to that extend
that I knew to myself that am
beginning to cross the boundary of this earth.
But to God be the glory, I woke up one fateful morning
I prayed and said, "God, I have tried the doctors,
I have tried the world.
I have tried with my own strength and power
and they have all failed me.
Now I want to try you God.
Give me the strength and grace
to come to your presence and try your grace."
I said that prayer, I slept off; I woke up at
around at around 2:00 pm in the afternoon.
I felt some energy in me,
I felt some strength, I stood up.
I said, "Wow, I can move now,
I think I should go to Lagos now"
My mother asked, "Going to Lagos?"
I said, "Yes!"
She said, "how? you cant, don't."
I said, No! I am leaving to Lagos now."
They were trying to stop me, I said No!
She then came and said that she is coming with me.
that she will aid me down here.
Immediately she started packing my bag
After packing my bag it was almost 3pm.
I said we are still going to Lagos
that is how we left from onitsha to asaba.
we boarded a bus, we came down to Lagos.
And to God be the glory, I was privilege
to be among the people in the prayer line.
And our senior prophet in the Lord
The man God has bestowed all of Him upon.
Laid just one hand.
[Applause]
This is me that was medically rejected and contempt.
I was told that I was going to die, it was painful.
but it was just a touch from God.
He raised his hand and he stretched it,
and I saw the hand of God moving with his hand.
Immediately he touched me, I felt as if the sick cloud
has left me, I saw myself on the ground.
I stood up, I felt so light;
I felt like a baby, I felt like I am new.
I felt different, I was confused
I was just thinking what happened.
He went around, he came again;
he stood and he looked at me.
I wanted to say something,
he touched my stomach again.
Immediately it was like as if something
like a giant moved and left me.
And i felt that again, and i stood up.
and he said, "You are healed in Jesus name."
He said, "Go Jesus has healed you."
In me as human, I was still having that doubt.
I thought, "Doctors condemned me,
they said they could not help me,
how can just a touch take care of everything?"
I went back to the hotel where
we lodged, I slept off.
I woke up late in the evening around after 6:00pm,
I then remembered that there was
retro viral drugs they gave me.
That helped control those symptoms
like those shaking and all that.
That if you If I don't take it, you will find me shaking
and dancing and you will run away.
You would think that I want to die.
I remembered that I have not taken my pills.
I told her, "I haven't taken my pills."
She told me, "Take those pills now
before those symptom starts,"
She was always afraid whenever
those symptoms come up.
that I should please take them, she rushed
and brought those pills.
and a glass of water.
And I said to her, "I wont take those pills again.
so long as this symptoms did not
come up from church to back home here.
That means I am healed, I wont take those pills again."
And while I left the prayer
line I was blessed with this morning water.
I went home also and ministered it with my family,
because I knew I become strong.
I had this strength in me, that
I could now stand and call my family together
Make prayer with them and minister the anointing water
upon each and everyone of them.
And then minister upon my self.
Immediately i ministered into my mouth it went down
as if it was a cold block I had swallowed
It went down and all my body
inside my system become cold
It was like something was reviving in me.
Like there is something going on inside.
After which, I smiled and said, "God is at work."
Then a week later, I went back to those doctors.
I said, "Doctor, I want to do this test again,"
He said, "what test?"
I said," the hepatitis B test"
He said, "You should be talking about your
treatment, you are talking about test,
take you pills and go."
I said, "I want to do this test again."
They did the test and it showed
non reactive which is negative.
{Shall we put our hands together,
that
clap is not loud enough for Jesus.
Put your hands together, Louder, louder louder
for the miracle working God, hallelujah!
We know only Jesus could have just done this
Did you just hear what our brother said?
He said he was a living dead,
he was just living but he was already gone.
Because doctors had already
condemned him dead,
as there was nothing they could
have done about that sickness
because today in the world we
know that it is non curable.
But for him to come and just a touch,
just a touch of Gods finger,
through his anointed servant eradicated all
those virus of Hepatitis B.
Just a week later he went back to the hospital to do another test
And it proved negative.
Who can do that? Its non other but, JESUS!
If you know that, put your hands together for Jesus!
Hallelujah!}
Then the doctor saw the result and
he said, "No there is a mistake somewhere."
"May be there is a mistake."
I said, "what mistake?"
He said that there is a mistake.
I said there is no mistake
He said, "no!"
He called on the lab technician attendant
and asked, "What is the problem?
what sort of mistake is this?
go and rerun this test again."
They called me back to the lab room
they took the samples and they re run the test.
I waited in the hospital for about 30 minutes.
The results came out again, It showed,
non reactive which means negative.
the doctor asked, "Is this magic?"
I said, "magic?"
He said, "yes"
I said, "you doctors, you treat;
who heals and who cures?"
He said God.
I said I visited God.
He then looked at me and said, "my friend,
don't be deceived by all this magic."
they are just magics, that I
should just stick to my drugs.
So that I may have more days to live,
if not you will just go and die
all this people are just magicians.
I just looked at him and told him, "God bless you!"
and I left his office.
I went to another doctor that I met that ran from me
and said, "I am here for this same test,
I want to confirm it."
They did the test again, It showed negative
The doctor looked at me and said, "what happened?"
I said, "Doctor, I went to the Synagogue Church of All Nations and I met with God."
Immediately the doctor called
the nurses and showed them the results.
The nurses started jumping and dancing
they left all the patients they were attending to
and they were all dancing in the hospital.
If you saw the way they were dancing,
shouting and singing praises
I was just looking at them, they were
all hugging me one after the other.
Thanking God for my life.
And everybody was so happy.
I went back home, my mum looked at me.
In the compound where i live,
everybody was dancing and singing
and we were all happy.
And to God be the glory, I stayed and stayed
I had to go back for the test to confirm
It showed negative
I smiled within me.
A year after, i was still living and i said,
"Oh doctors said I was going to die soon,
and here I am alive."
This is two years now, I am alive
healthy, stronger as you can see.
{Put your hands together once again for Jesus.
If Jesus say yes, no one can say no,
Jesus Christ is the master healer and we have seen
the prove in the life of our brother.
Who is a living testimony.}
This is the hepatitis B genotypes,
as you can see here they all show positives
It shows that the were all detected
As you can see here.
Then this is the hepatitis B DNA, as you can see here.
this is the viral load and the DNA
as you can see
It shows that it is there on the higher side.
This is also another confirmation
from federal medical center Asaba
It shows positive, that was before I came to the Synagogue Church of All Nations.
This was after my encounter with
God through senior prophet TB Joshua
I went back and I did another test,
and here it says non reactive,
which is negative.
Weeks later, I still went back for another confirmation,
and it still shows the same report,
non reactive - which is negative.
I wasn't satisfied, to clear my doubt;
I had to go and do retro viral screening
which means all viral infection tests.
And they all showed negative including
HIV, everything showed negative.
The person next beside me is my very good friend.
I am very very happy to stand here
to testify
the goodness of God in my friends life.
Back in 2014, he was very very bad
The sickness was very bad with him,
he could not talk, walk or eat.
I used to call him then letter 'I'
because he was slim as letter 'I'
The doctors said that he wont make it,
that even if he wastes all his money
that he was not going to make it.
But today he is alive for the glory of God.
{Yes we have heard from the friend who
is a witness to the condition that the brother was in
before he came to the SCOAN.
And now that God almighty has
healed him she is a witness
and she is telling us of God goodness in his life.
So tell us now, or demonstrate to
us the things you can do now.
which you could not do before.}
Before, I know when they say that
some people are walking corpse
mind how you act, dont slap somebody, dont fight
you might just slap him and he die;
he is a walking corpse.
With my experience then, i knew what a
walking corpse really was.
because I couldn't do anything on my own
But now, If you can permit me, i can
climb up this stare case and jump from there.
I can.....
I am strong now, I can do anything.
I go to my sport and exercise
I run 10 km every morning
I do my training, all those things i couldn't do; I do.
Like before, I couldn't eat
for like five months i was on vegetables and fruits.
But now I eat anything I see comfortably,
no problem anymore.
As you see me now, I can say
I am even stronger than anybody here.
My advice for the viewers all over the world,
especially the youths.
Is that 'God is the author and finisher of our faith.'
Our prophet always says, '
When we sin, we should not run away
from God rather we should run to God.'
And also the Bible made it well known that
sickness is from the pit of hell.
and the only thing that attracts sickness, I know of now.
Is sinfull nature.
My advice to viewers all over the world is to run to God.
keep close to him, do his will,
obey his commandments and
you will find yourself flying like a wind.
like an eagle
My advice to them now is,
don't listen to what people say.
come and confirm yourself.
The Lord Jesus who is the same,
yesterday, today and forevermore is here
even right now as i am speaking he is here.
{ Hallelujah! we thank you for that wonderful advice
As our brother has said,
that God almighty never
disconnect Himself from those who
make mistakes with their lives.
He loves them and welcomes them,
and you know that forgiveness
of sins strikes the roots of all things.
And as you are equally being advised
to find out the truth, and that truth shall set us free.
We give God all mighty all the
Glory for what He has done in your life,
for restoring back your health.
And making you a living testimony
to the goodness of God,
and the lives of the people.
And now that the Lord almighty has set you free,
Remember that is for non other but
for the salvation of your soul.
So make sure you continue to follow him along the way,
and make his word the standard for your life.
And I know His Word will continue to
set you on the good road to the good life.}
Amen!
{So once again let us put our hands together wonderfully for our lord and Savior Jesus Christ!}